mindbatteries.com 2016-11-18

# Privacy

**WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY**

This website privacy policy (“ **Privacy Policy** ” or “ **Policy** ”) describes Agile Chandigarh’s (the “ **Firm** ” or “ **Company** ”) policies on collection, use, and disclosure of information about you in connection with your use of the domain, [www.mindbatteries.com](https://www.mindbatteries.com/) (“ **Site** ” or “ **Website** ”) owned and controlled by the Company. The terms “ **we** ”, “ **us** ” or “ **our** ”, refer to [www.mindbatteries.com](http://www.mindbatteries.com/) or the Company, used interchangeably. The Company is an intermediary service providing platform providing targeted services for spreading of education and serving it on an entertainment, educational and professional platter. In order to provide the services, we ask for certain personal information which is displayed on the Site. When you use the service available at our Website, you consent to our collection, use, and disclosure of information about yourself as described in this Privacy Policy. For purpose of this Policy, the term ‘service’ shall mean, besides definition(s) provided in User Agreement, with respect to any electronic record, storing or transmitting that record or providing any service with respect to that electronic record, including online education, events, corporate internships, market place discovery platform, learning, teaching or any other service explicitly mentioned and displayed on the Site and User Agreement.

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a revised Privacy Policy on this page.  Such changes will be effective upon posting.

In every respect, by using the Site, you agree to be bound by terms of this Privacy Policy.

**1\. INTRODUCTION**

1.1 Your privacy is important to you and to us. We’ll protect the information you share with us. To protect your privacy, the Site follows different principles in accordance with worldwide practices for customer privacy and data protection.

1.2 We, at the Company are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information (“ **Personal Information** ”) you share with us. For purpose of this Policy, Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit the Site’s web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself. If however, Personal Information is revealed to us, we won’t sell or give away any content of your Personal Information to anyone except our channel partners, including people who may be involved in the delivery of service.  

**2\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT**

2.1 When you visit the Site or use our Service, we collect and store information about you, your computer or mobile device and your activities. This information may include, but is not limited to:

2.2.1 Your computer’s IP address; technical information about your computer or mobile device (such as type of device, web browser or operating system).

2.2.2 Your mobile device’s unique ID number (when available), your mobile device’s geographic location (specific geographic location if you’ve enabled collection of that information, or general geographic location automatically).

2.2.3 Your provided full name, email address, zip code and other information you may provide with your account, such as your gender and birth date. You may optionally provide us with this information through third party sign-in services such as Facebook and Google Plus. In such cases, we fetch and store whatever information is made available to us by you through these sign-in services.

2.2.4 How long you visited our service and which features you used.

2.2.5 We gather information from members and guests who apply for the various Services that our site offers. It includes, but may not be limited to, email address, first name, last name, a user-specified password, e-mail Id, mailing address, zip code and telephone number or fax number. We collect information primarily to ensure that we are able to fulfill your requirements and to deliver personalized experience.

**3\. NOTICE**

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you create a registration or login ID on the Site or when you connect or browse connected sites, linked or listed on our Website, or join a limited-access premium site.

**4\. CONSENT AND SHARING OF INFORMATION**

The information collected from our users or visitors is shared with members and stakeholders of the Company, namely; sponsors, third party advisors, mentors, companies, employees, stakeholders and other experts who are part of the network of community of [www.mindbatteries.com](https://www.mindbatteries.com/) . Any information you give us is held with the utmost care and security. We are also bound to cooperate fully should a situation arise where we are required by law or legal process to provide information about a customer.

**5\. ACCESS**

We will provide you with the means to ensure that your Personal Information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at any time at the login section. There, you can:

  * view and edit personal information you have already given us;

  * tell us whether you want us to send you marketing information;  

  * sign up for electronic newsletters about our services and products.

**6\. SECURITY**

6.1 The Site has taken strong measures to protect the security of your Personal Information and to ensure that your choices for its intended use are honoured. We take strong precautions to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can see or edit your Personal Information without knowing your user name and password, so do not share these with others.

6.2 We however do not guarantee your e-commerce transactions to be entirely safe and secure. When you place orders through our Website or online payment gateway service providers (“ **OPGSPs** ”) listed on the Site. You must ensure that you agree to the terms and conditions of the said OPGSPs agreement. The Company shall not be liable should there be a discrepancy in refund, loss or misuse of credit card details, hacking of sensitive monetary information.

6.3 Resolution of all payment related complaints shall remain the responsibility of OPGSPs concerned. Users must read and agree to privacy policy and online security framework of respective OPGSPs listed on the Site before transacting. We do not take responsibility for any security lapse, should infringement or violation happen as a result of you accessing an OPGSP listed on the Site.

**7\. NOTICE TO PARENTS**

We want to help you guard your children’s privacy. We encourage you to talk to your children about safe and responsible use of their Personal Information while using our Site. The Site does not publish content that is harmful, derogatory or pornographic in nature. However, the Website shall not incur any liability should your children provide us any Personal Information without parental consent. If you become aware that a child has provided us with personal information without parental consent, please contact us at [www.mindbatteries.com](https://www.mindbatteries.com/). If we become aware that a child has provided us with Personal Information without parental consent, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child’s account.  

**8\. COOKIES**

When you visit our Site, we may place “cookies” on your computer to recognize you. We do this to store your preferences, collect statistical data and track your use of our Service. Cookies are widely used, and most web browsers are configured initially to accept cookies automatically. If you prefer not to accept cookies, you may adjust and configure your browser settings accordingly. However, if you turn off cookies, or refuse to accept a request to place a cookie, some features and services on the Site may not function properly. Ad companies (including but not limited to Google and Facebook) may also place cookies on your computer to track your activities across various sites so that they can display targeted advertisements.

**9\. WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION YOU SHARE**

9.1 When you join us, you provide us with your contact information, including your name and email address. We use this information to send you updates about our Services, questionnaires to measure your satisfaction with our Service and announcements about new and exciting services that we offer.  

9.2 We will disclose your Personal Information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) confirm to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on the Site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of the Company; and (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Company or the public.

**10\. INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE  **

10.1 The Company does not rent or sell Personal Information about you with other people (save with your consent) or non-affiliated companies, except to provide services you’ve requested, under the following circumstances:

  * We provide the information to trusted partners, affiliates, mentors, industry experts and successful entrepreneurs (collectively “ **Service Partners** ”) only if we the necessity to do so in order to enhance your Website experience. Service Partners may use your Personal Information to help us communicate with you about offers from the Website. However, Service Partners do not have any independent right to share this information.

  * We respond to court orders, legal process or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Website’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

  * We shall transfer information about you only if the Company is acquired by another company or individual. In this event, the Website will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

  * We may need to contact you to comply or co-operate with a legal request. For this purpose, we will use the email address provided to us by you. All communications sent by us at such email address shall be deemed to have been communicated to you.

10.2 **Data disclosure to OPGSPs** : We may disclose your personal information to OPGSPs and for the following purposes:

10.2.1 to prevent, detect, mitigate, and investigate potentially illegal acts, fraud and/or security breaches, and to assess and manage risk, including to alert you if fraudulent activities have been detected on your user accounts;

10.2.2 to provide customer services, including to help service your account or resolve disputes (e.g., billing or transactional disputes);

10.2.3 to facilitate the processing of payment cards when you pay within our Services with a payment card and we use OPGSPs to process your payment.

10.3 **Disclosure to Service Providers and financial institutions partners** :

Third party service providers who help us to provide our Services, payment processing services, assist us in providing customize advertising, to assist us with the prevention, detection, mitigation, and investigation of potentially illegal acts, violations of our User Agreement, fraud and/or security breaches, bill collection, affiliate and rewards programs, co-branded credit cards and other business operations.

**11\. CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY**

11.1 We limit access to Personal Information about you to employees and stakeholders who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

11.2   We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with the laws prevalent in India to protect personal information about you. We seek to ensure compliance with the requirements of the information technology laws as applicable from time to time to ensure the protection and preservation of your privacy. Additionally, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or via mobile device, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**12\. YOUR CONSENT  **

By using the Website, you consent to the terms of our Website Privacy Policy and to the Site’s processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above as well as those explained where we at the Company collect personal information on the web.

**13\. PRIVACY POLICY CONCERNS AND GRIEVANCE REDRESSAL MECHANISM**

If you have any grievance relating to the processing/usage of information provided by you or the Site’s Privacy Policy, you may email our Grievance Officer at [legal@mindbatteries.com](mailto:legal@mindbatteries.com).   

**14\. CONTACT INFORMATION  **

We welcome your comments regarding this privacy statement at the contact address given at the website. Should there be any concerns about contravention of this Privacy Policy, we will employ all commercially reasonable efforts to address the same. The terms in this Policy may be changed by us at any time. Should you have concerns regarding this Policy or the Services that we offer, please feel free to write to us at: contact[@mindbatteries.com](mailto:feedback@mindbatteries.com).  

**15\. JURISDICTION**  
www.mindbatteries.com is controlled by Agile Chandigarh, a partnership firm registered under the Indian Partnership Act, 1938. The Site can be accessed by most countries around the world. By accessing the Site you summarily agree to exclusive jurisdiction of courts in Chandigarh, India only and that in general Indian laws governing international service contracts shall apply.

IN WITNESS WHEREOF, all users or visitors of the Site agree that they have read the Terms of Use mentioned in this Agreement and agree to be bound by them for as long as they continue to either use the Site or avail Services of the Company.
